Question 1-3
This is an automated message
from the Minson Pharmaceutical Company to all employees.
1 Due to the severe weather predicted for this afternoon,
the company president has decided to close the office early, at two P.M.
2 Local weather reports indicate that temperatures are dropping quickly,
and roads will likely become slippery by early evening.
3 As a precaution, please remember to shut down your computers
before you leave.
This will prevent any damage
that a storm-related power failure may cause.
Thank you.
Question 4-6
Hi, this is Jackie Gross, from Human Resources.
4 Congratulations on your promotion to manager of our Thailand office!
I'm calling because I've been asked to assist you with your move overseas.
5 The first thing I'll do is get in touch with a moving company
to estimate the cost of the move.
6 I also need to conﬁrm your passport number for your work visa;
I want to make sure your paperwork is in order as soon as possible.
Please call me back at your earliest convenience.
Question 7-9
Hello, this message is for Mr. Lehman.
7 This is Mei Li from Sun Central Pharmacy.
I'm calling to let you know that
your doctor called in your prescription for allergy pills earlier today.
8 We usually have that medication in stock,
but unfortunately, we ran out yesterday.
We'll get a new shipment in tomorrow, though.
Your prescription will be ready for you to pick up after two P.M.
9 Please come by the front desk of the pharmacy when you stop in tomorrow.
Thank you and have a good evening.
Question 10-12
Anwei! 10 Thank you so much for helping set up
for the party after last night's theater performance.
I couldn't have done it without you,
and 11 the spicy dish you brought was delicious!
You have got to tell me where you found the recipe!
Everyone really liked it, and it didn't look too complicated.
12 Anyway, I guess I'll see you Monday.
I think we have rehearsal together for Elia Grande's new play.
I'm really excited to get started.
Question 13-15
Thank you for calling the offices of Clifton Associates.
13 Our lawyers are committed to providing you with the best legal services in the Belmont area.
14 Currently, we are closed as we relocate to our new offices at 46 Spencer Street.
If your call is urgent, please leave a message after the tone
- our associate 15 Catherine Walsh is checking our voice-mail system regularly
and will be able to relay your message.
For all other matters, we look forward to speaking with you personally
when our office reopens on Tuesday. Thank you.
Question 16-18
Hello, this is SyIvia Chen. I recentIy purchased a camera from your online shop.
16 Unfortunately, when the camera arrived, the lens was scratched.
17I want to bring it to the post office this afternoon to return it for an exchange,
but I'd like to speak to someone from your company before I mail it.
You see, I'm moving to a new house next week,
so the replacement will have to be shipped to my new address.
18 Please call me back so I can be sure your shipping department will send the camera to the correct address.
Question 19-21
Hi, this message is for Peter in room scheduling.
This is Colin O'Donnell. I want to change my room reservation.
19 I have the Presidential Library reserved for 9:00 this morning for a meeting with clients.
However, I realize that that's not going to work, because I'm serving refreshments to the clients.
20 I noticed that my colleague Sylvia has a meeting at the same time, and maybe she could switch rooms with me.
Could you check with her, please, and conﬁrm that I can use the room that she signed up for?
21 I'm showing a video to the clients, so I need to tell the audiovisual support group where to help me set up the equipment.